The First Ninja Commandos
Ultimax Force is a action film directed by Willy Milan.
The ULTIMAX FORCE, an elite group of Commandos, a force
combining the skills of a Ninja warrior with U.S.
Commando training, penetrate deep into Vietnamese territory.
Their mission - to liberate a POW camp run by a sadistic colonel, who has mercilessly slaughtered his prisoners
in a display of rabid madness and butchery; a challenge which, for them, is the ULTIMATE MAXIMUM.
Chris Burton, played by Arnold Nicholas.
Dick Foster, played by Jeremy Ladd.
Bill Norton, played by Brad Cassini.
Colonel Minh, played by Rey Vhen.
Mike Dobson, played by Vincent Giffin.
Phoung, played by Vivian Cheung.
The following is a list of films where at least one ninja
character appears as a significant plot element.
The film explores themes of vietnam, prisoner of war, ninja, ninja warrior.
The tone is thought_provoking.